Guide to the Matthew Vassar Papers, 1730-1975
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series III. Matthew Vassar and Company, Brewers
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to George P. Oakley (original in New York Public Library), 31 Mar 1830; (1 letter) (Folder 15.372)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Mears L. Booridge, Co., 15 Nov 1834; (1 letter) (Folder 15.373)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Gentlemen, 29 Jan 1835; (1 letter) (Folder 15.374)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Matthew Vassar, Jr., 26 Sep 1836; (1 letter) (Folder 15.375)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Matthew Vassar, Jr., 27 Sep 1836; (1 letter) (Folder 15.376)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Matthew Vassar, Jr., 30 Sep 1836; (1 letter) (Folder 15.377)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to [?], 30 Sep 1836; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.378)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 2 Nov 1836; (1 letter) (Folder 15.379)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 7 Nov 1836; (1 letter) (Folder 14.380)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 10 Nov 1836; (1 letter) (Folder 15.381)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 11 Nov 1836; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.382)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 16 Nov 1836; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.383)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Nov 1836; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.384)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 23 Nov 1836; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.385)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 24 Nov 1836; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.386)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Whinfield, Henry, Civil Engineer to Vassar, Co., 6 Jan 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.387)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 9 Jan 1837; (1 letter) (Folder 15.388)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 10 Jan 1837; (1 letter) (Folder 14.389)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 26 Apr 1837; (1 letter) (Folder 15.390)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 1 Sep 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.391)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 5 Oct 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.392)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 17 Oct 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.393)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 18 Oct 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.394)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Oct 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.395)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 24 Oct 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.396)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 26 Oct 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.397)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 30 Oct 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.398)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 1 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.399)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 4 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.400)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 5 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.401)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 8 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.402)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 14 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.403)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Gentlemen, 16 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.404)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Gentlemen, 16 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.405)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.406)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 15.407)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.408)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.409)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 22 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.410)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 25 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.411)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.412)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Nov 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.413)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Nov 1837; (1 letter) (Folder 16.414)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 1 Dec 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.415)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 1 Dec 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.416)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 2 Dec 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.417)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 4 Dec 1837; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.418)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Jan 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.419)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 9 Feb 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.420)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 12 Feb 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.421)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 17 Feb 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.422)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Feb 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.423)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 23 Feb 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.424)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 26 Mar 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.425)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 27 Mar 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.426)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Mar 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.427)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Apr 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.428)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Apr 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.429)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 21 Apr 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.430)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 23 Apr 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.431)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 22 Jun 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.432)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 14 Aug 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.433)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 15 Aug 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.434)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 18 Aug 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.435)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 21 Aug 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.436)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 21 Aug 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.437)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 6 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.438)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to [?], 10 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.439)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 12 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.440)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to J. Hartbottle, Co., 17 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.441)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 17 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.442)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 19 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.443)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.444)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 21 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.445)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 25 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.446)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 26 Sep 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.447)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 1 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.448)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 2 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.449)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 4 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.450)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 8 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.451)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 9 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.452)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 10 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.453)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 11 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.454)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 11 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 16.455)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 16 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.456)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.457)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 24 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.458)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 27 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.459)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 31 Oct 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.460)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 1 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.461)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 1 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.462)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 2 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.463)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 9 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.464)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 10 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.465)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 10 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.466)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 17 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.467)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.467A)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.468)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 21 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.469)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Matthew Vassar Co., 22 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.470)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 23 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.471)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 24 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.472)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 25 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.473)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Gentlemen, 30 Nov 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.474)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 13 Dec 1838; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.475)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Jan 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.476)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 30 Jan 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.477)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 16 Feb 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.478)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Feb 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.479)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Feb 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.480)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Feb 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.481)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 22 Feb 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.482)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 13 Mar 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.483)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 27 Mar 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.484)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Mar 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.485)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 30 Mar 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.486)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 5 Jun 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.487)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Sep 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.488)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Sep 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.489)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 4 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.490)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 5 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.491)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 7 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.492)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 10 Oct 1839; (1 letter) (Folder 14.493)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 11 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.494)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 17 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.495)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.496)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.497)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.498)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 22 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.499)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 23 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 17.500)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 24 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.501)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.502)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 29 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.503)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 31 Oct 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.504)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 5 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.505)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 6 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.506)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 7 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.507)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 12 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.508)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 13 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.509)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 14 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.510)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 16 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.511)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.512)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 19 Nov 1839; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.513)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 24 Jan 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.514)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 27 Jan 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.515)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 28 Jan 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.516)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 31 Jan 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.517)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 1 Feb 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.518)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 17 Mar 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.519)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Mar 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.520)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Mar 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.521)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 25 Mar 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.522)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 16 Apr 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.523)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, May [1840?]; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.524)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 21 May 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.525)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 25 May 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.526)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Jun 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.527)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 25 Jun 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.528)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 11 Jul 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.529)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 8 Oct 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.530)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Oct 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.531)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 21 Oct 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 18.532)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 17 Nov 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.533)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Nov 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.534)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Nov 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.535)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 2 Dec 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.536)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 8 Dec 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.537)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 8 Dec 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.538)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 10 Dec 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.539)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 11 Dec 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.540)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 11 Dec 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.541)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 12 Dec 1840; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.542)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 16 Jul 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.543)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 17 Jul 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.544)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Jul 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.545)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Jul 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.546)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 21 Jul 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.547)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Aug 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.548)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 20 Aug 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.549)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 30 Aug 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.550)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 7 Sep 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.551)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 8 Sep 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.552)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 8 Sep 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.553)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Sep 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.554)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 29 Sep 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.555)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 7 Oct 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.556)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 12 Oct 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.557)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Oct 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.558)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Oct 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.559)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 25 Oct 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.560)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 27 Oct 1841; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.561)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 14 Sep 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.562)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 15 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.563)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 17 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.564)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 18 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.565)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 22 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.566)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 23 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.567)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 25 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.568)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 26 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.569)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 26 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.570)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 27 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 19.571)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 28 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 14.572)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 29 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.573)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 31 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.574)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 31 Oct 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.575)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Gentlemen, 3 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.576)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Gentlemen, 6 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.577)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 12 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.578)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 14 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.579)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 19 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.580)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 21 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.581)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 24 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.582)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 27 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.583)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 31 Dec 1842; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.584)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Gentlemen, 5 Jan 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.585)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 10 Jan 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.586)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 12 Jan 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.587)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 30 Jan 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.588)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 1 Feb 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.589)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sirs, 2 Feb 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.590)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 3 Feb 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.591)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 8 Feb 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.592)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 14 Feb 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.593)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 24 Feb 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.594)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 26 Aug 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.595)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Harvey Edwards, 28 Aug 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.596)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 6 Oct 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.597)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 12 Oct 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.598)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 15 Oct 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.599)
  - Matthew Vassar, Co., correspondence: Vassar to Dear Sir, 25 Oct 1843; (1 letter)** (Folder 20.601)